

Summary.

My research interests include computational photography and computer vision. I'm familiar in Python, JavaScript, Shell, and other related programming languages. Besides research, I take a strong interest in photography, travel, and video games. My publications can be referred to https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=e_nu_TIAAAAJ&hl=zh-CN&authuser=1

Education

Johns Hopkins University

Maryland, US

ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING - FIRST-YEAR PHD STUDENT

Sep. 2021 -

• supervised by Prof. Vishal M. Patel.

The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen

Shenzhen, China

COMPUTER AND INFORMATION ENGINEERING - MASTER OF PHILOSOPHY (GPA: 3.5/4)

Sep. 2019 - Jun. 2021

• 2019-2021 Research Assistant Scholarship

Jiangxi Normal University

Nangchang, Chian

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY - BACHELOR (GPA: 3.4/4) GRADUATED WITH HIGH DISTINCTION

Sep. 2015 - Jun. 2019

• 2015-2016 University Scholarship / China Telecommunications Scholarship

Experience _____

DAMO Academy, Alibaba-Group

RESEARCH INTERN

Jul. 2020 - OCt. 2020

• Worked on automatic old film reparation in the help of GAN inversion under limited dataset.

Kwai Technology

IMAGE ALGORITHM ENGINEER INTERN

Jul. 2018 - Jun. 2019

· Worked on improving the photography capability of low-quality mobile cameras by Deep Learning.

JD.COM

SOFTWARE ARCHITECTURE ENGINEER INTERN

Jul. 2017 - Nov. 2017

• Worked on Intelligent Poster Generation System as a front-end software engineer.

Honors & Awards

INTERNATIONAL

2019	1st Place , Advances in Image Manipulation Challenges (RAW2RGB) in conjunction with ICCV 2019	Seoul, Korea
2019	Oral, Learning for Computational Imaging (LCI) Workshop in conjunction with ICCV 2019	Seoul, Korea
2018	6th Place and Honorable Mention Award, NTIRE-CVPR 2018 (Dehazing)	Salt Lake City, US

DOMESTIC

2019	4th Place and Geek Award , Alibaba-Youku Video Enhancement and Super Resolution Challenge (4/1514)	Hangzhou, China
2018	3rd Place , Single Image Dehazing Challenge in conjunction with ChinaMM 2018	Xian, China
2018	Gold Award & Best innovative Award, University Programming Challenge in Pearl River Delta (1/3000~)	Macau, China
2017	24th Place, JD.COM Potential User Prediction (24/4240)	Beijing, China
2016	2nd Award, National Computer Program Design Challenge	Shanghai, China

Research.

Connections Exploration between The Image Restoration and Understanding

FADER

Jul. 2018 - Present

• In the research, my works mainly focus on improving the performance low-level vision tasks, e.g., super-resolution, de-hazing, and enlighten with high-level vision features. As well as improving the high-level vision tasks, i.e., semantic segmentation on restored degraded scenes with image enhancement technologies.

Academic Service _____

Reviewer of IJCV/TIP/TMM/TCSVT/CVIU/SPL/CVPR22

DECEMBER 7, 2021 KANGFU MEI · RÉSUMÉ 1